Hello everyone and welcome to this just in my name is Marco and my name is Catherine
Hello everyone and we have for you today a very special this just in like fresh fresh news. It's so fresh
We had to have an extra show this week
Exactly. So what's actually happening is that on Monday you're going to notice that our website is gonna change just a little bit
Yeah, so you might not recognize it completely, but it will be the same website
And the reason for this is that we are changing the website for our Chinese users
Which means that if you are using a computer in China what you see will be different if you're in China
And you log on to English pod comm you see an option
It says would you like to be a Chinese language user or an English language user?
But if you're anywhere else in the world Brazil Russia America any any any other country you won't see this
All you'll see is a new prettier more beautiful English pod comm right so there will be a couple of small changes with the tabs
You won't have a me section anymore, but it's gonna be a little bit different
So it'll take you a little bit of time to get used to it, but it's really nice the website
It's made to be a little bit more efficient and what we promised you a website about six months ago
So now here it is
Exactly, and so we're really excited that we've finally been able to bring this to you
It's a great improvement, and if you have any questions or comments about how to use it what you like
What you don't like we'd love to hear those so please send them to us our email address is support at practice language comm
But you can also post on the website itself
That's right your comments your questions and your suggestions for the website are very valuable because if you find bugs
Or if you find something is a little bit difficult or anything in general you can just tell us and we'll definitely take your input
Exactly, so that's gonna be it for our special Sunday's news update
But hopefully this is a good update for most of you and again if you have questions let us know all right
We'll see you guys Monday with our great new lessons till next time